Guide to the Adler hip hop archive, circa 1970-2013.
Adler hip hop archive
- Series I. News Files
  - News Files 1990s and 2000s
    - Performer Names A-H
      - Funkmaster Flex a/k/a Funk Flex
        - Funk Flex Flyers, 2003-2013 (Box 21, Folder 49)
        - Funkmaster Flex, 2000-2007 (Box 21, Folder 50)
      - Funkytown Pros, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 51)
      - Fu-Schnickens, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 52)
      - Future, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 53)
      - Kether Gallu-Badat, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 54)
      - Kether Gallu-Badat, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 55)
      - Game, 2005-2011 (Box 21, Folder 56)
      - Game (magazine)/J Shecter, c. 2001 (Box 21, Folder 57)
      - Gangsta Boo, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 58)
      - Bobbito Garcia, 1993-1994, 2002-2013 (Box 21, Folder 59)
      - Bill Gates, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 60)
      - Gee Street Records, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 61)
      - Gerardo, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Ghostface Killah, 2000-2013 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Robert Glasper, 2012 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Ginuwine, 1999-2005 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Gnarls Barkley, 2006-2008 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - The Goats, 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Geto Boys, 1990-2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Goodie Mob, 1996-2009 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Irv Gotti, 1999-2006 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Jean Grae, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Grand Daddy I.U., 1990-1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Grand Puba, 1992-2001 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Gravediggaz, 1994-1997, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Julie Greenwald, 2010-2011 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Group Home, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Gucci Mane, 2007-2011 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Stacy Gueraseva, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Guerilla Black, No Date (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - GZA a/k/a Genius; GZA/Genius, 1996-2012 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - The Hard Corps, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - David Harleston, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Heather B, 1995-2001 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Heltah Skeltah, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Jimmy Henchman, 2013 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Hieroglyphics, No Date (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - "Hip Hop: A Cultural Odyssey" (book), 2011 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Hip Hop Tours, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - H.W.A. (Hoes With Attitudes), 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Honey (magazine), 2001 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Hot Boys, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - House of Pain, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - "How High" (movie), 2001 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Heather Hunter, No Date (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - Hurricane Chris, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - "Hustle and Flow" (movie), 2005 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Performer Names I-P
      - Ice Cube
        - Ice Cube "Amerikkka's Most Wanted", 1990 (Box 22, Folder 36)
        - Ice Cube photos, 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 37)
        - Ice Cube '91, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 38)
        - Ice Cube '92, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 39)
        - Ice Cube/Angela Davis conversation, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 40)
        - Jeff Chang re Ice Cube's "Black Korea", 1993 (Box 22, Folder 41)
        - Ice Cube '93, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 42)
        - Ice Cube '94, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 43)
        - Ice Cube '95, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 44)
        - Ice Cube '00-'08, 2000-2008 (Box 22, Folder 45)
        - Ice Cube '05-'12, 2005-2012 (Box 22, Folder 46)
      - Ill Al Scratch, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 47)
      - Ill one, 200-2001 (Box 22, Folder 48)
      - Illegal, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 49)
      - Immortal Technique, 2006-2013 (Box 22, Folder 50)
      - Insane Clown Posse, 1998-2012 (Box 22, Folder 51)
      - Inspectah Deck, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 52)
      - The Intelligent Hoodlum, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 53)
      - Invisibl Skratch Piklz, No Date (Box 22, Folder 54)
      - Isis, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 55)
      - Jacki-O, 2003-2005 (Box 22, Folder 56)
      - Jacob the Jeweler, 1999-2013 (Box 22, Folder 57)
      - Jadakiss, 2001-2011 (Box 22, Folder 58)
      - Jagged Edge, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 59)
      - Billy Jam, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 60)
      - Jamal-Ski, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 61)
      - Ja Rule, 2002-2013 (Box 22, Folder 62)
      - "Jason's Lyric" (movie), 1994 (Box 22, Folder 63)
      - Jayo Felony, 1995-2001 (Box 22, Folder 64)
      - Jay-Z
        - Jay-Z photos, 1995, No Date (Box 22, Folder 65)
        - Jay-Z bios, 1995-2005 (Box 22, Folder 66)
        - Jay-Z '90s, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 67)
        - Jay-Z ads, 1996-2009 (Box 22, Folder 68)
        - Jay-Z copies of magazines '98-'01, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 69)
        - Jay-Z '00-'03, 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 70)
        - Jay-Z '04, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 71)
        - Jay-Z "99 Problems" (uncut version of music video), DVD-1182 (Box 22, Folder 71)
          Directed by Mark Romanek
        - Jay-Z '05, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 72)
        - Jay-Z '06, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 73)
        - Jay-Z '07-'10, 2007-2010 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - Jay-Z '11-'12, 2011-2012 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Jay-Z '13, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Jaz-O/Big Jaz, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - J. Cole, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - J Dilla, 2006-2007 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Wyclef Jean, 1997-2013 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Jerky Boys, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Jeru the Damaja, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Gaye T. Johnson, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Jim Jones, 2006-2012 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Mike Jones, 2006-2009 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Miss Jones, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Montell Jordan, 1994-2002 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - JT the Bigga Figga, 1994-1995, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - "Juice" (movie), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Juicy J, 2012-2013 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Junior Mafia, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Jurassic 5, 2000-2006 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - "Just For Kicks" (movie about hip-hop and sneakers), 2005-2009 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Juvenile, 1998-2009 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Kam, 1993-2005 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Kane and Abel, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - K-Ci and JoJo, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - K-Dee, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Kelis, 2000-2010 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - R. Kelly
        - R. Kelly, 2000-2012 (Box 23, Folder 27)
        - R. Kelly '00-'13, 2000-2013 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Erica Kennedy, 1999-2012 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Khia, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Kid Capri, 1996-2004 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Kid Cudi, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Killah Priest, 1998-2001 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Killer Mike, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - King Britt, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - King Just, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - King Tee, 1993-1995, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - KMD, 1991-1994, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - Suge Knight, 1994-2009 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - Knoc-Turn'Al, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - Bobby Konders, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Kool Keith, 1999-2012 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - Krazy Bone, 1999-2001 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Kris Kross, 1992-1993, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Kurious a/k/a Kurious Jorge, 1992-1994, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - Kurupt, 1999-2002 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - Kwame, 1991-1994, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - Talib Kweli, 2003-2013 (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - Kwest Tha Mad Ladd, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - L.A. Posse, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - L.A. (Los Angeles) Rap, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - L.A. (Los Angeles) riots, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - Lady Saw, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 53)
      - Lady Sovereign, 2006-2009 (Box 23, Folder 54)
      - Kendrick Lamar, 2012-2013 (Box 23, Folder 55)
      - Large Professor, 2002-2007 (Box 23, Folder 56)
      - Latin Alliance, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 57)
      - Leaders of the New School, 1991-1994, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 58)
      - LeShaun, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 59)
      - Barrington Levy a/k/a General Levy, 2000-2007 (Box 23, Folder 60)
      - Lifers Group, 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 61)
      - Chris Lighty
        - Chris Lighty business documents '94-'95, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 62)
        - Chris Lighty '99-'13, 1999-2013 (Box 23, Folder 63)
        - Chris Lighty copies of press clippings '07, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 64)
        - Chris Lighty dies 2012, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 65)
      - Lil B, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 66)
      - Lil Boosie, 2006-2009 (Box 23, Folder 67)
      - Lil Bow Wow, 2001-2010 (Box 23, Folder 68)
      - Lil Flip, 2003-2007 (Box 23, Folder 69)
      - Lil Jon, 2001-2010 (Box 23, Folder 70)
      - Lil Kim
        - Lil Kim '90s, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 71)
        - Lil Kim '00-'10, 2000-2010 (Box 23, Folder 72)
        - Lil Kim '11-'12, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 73)
      - Lil Mama, 2007-2013 (Box 23, Folder 74)
      - Lil Mo, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 75)
      - Lil Romeo, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 76)
      - Lil Troy, 1999-2001 (Box 23, Folder 77)
      - Lil Wayne, 2002-2013 (Box 23, Folder 78)
      - Kevin Liles, 2004-2009 (Box 23, Folder 79)
      - Kevin Liles interview (pt 2), No Date; CD-2144 (Box 23, Folder 79)
      - John Walker Linden, 2001-2012 (Box 23, Folder 80)
      - Lin Que, 1993-1996, 2006-2007 (Box 23, Folder 81)
      - Live Squad, 1992-2013 (Box 23, Folder 82)
      - Lloyd, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 83)
      - Loon, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 84)
      - Lord Finesse, 1992-1995, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 85)
      - Lord Tariq and Peter Gunz, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 86)
      - Lords of the Underground, 1992-1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - The Lost Boys, 1995-2001 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Loud Records, (1962) 1986-2001 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - The Lox, 1999-2007 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Ludacris
        - Ludacris, 2000-2010 (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Ludacris versus O'Reilly, 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Ludacris - ads, press, photos, bios, 2001-2011 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - The Luniz, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Jess Lyfe, No Date (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Kevin Lyttle, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Mac Mall, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Craig Mack, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Mack da Maniak, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Macklemore and Ryan Lewis, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Mack 10, 1995-2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Mad Lion, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Mad Skillz, 1995-2000, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Main Source, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Maino, 2010-2012 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Angie Martinez, 2000-2010 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Marxman, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Mase, 1998-2004 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Kedar Massenberg, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - Masta Ace, 1991-1995 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      - Masta Killah, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - Master P, 1993-2013 (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Masters at Work, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - MC Brains, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - MC Breed, 1993-1995, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - MC Eiht, 1994-1999 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - MC Paul Barman, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - MC Peaches, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - MC Ren, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - MC Solaar, 1993-1998, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - Mel-low, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - Mellow Man Ace, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - Memphis Bleek, 1998-2005 (Box 24, Folder 37)
      - "Menace II Society" (film, soundtrack), 1993 (Box 24, Folder 38)
      - Method Man
        - Method Man business and legal documents '93-'95, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 39)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 15
        - Method Man business documents '94-'98, 1994-1998 (Box 24, Folder 40)
          RESTRICTED until 2050 - Moved to Box 45, Folder 16
        - Method Man '98-'11, 1998-2011 (Box 24, Folder 41)
        - Method Man and Redman, 1994-1998 (Box 24, Folder 42)
          Press for Blackout (album), bios and clippings
      - M.I.A., 2010-2013 (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Mia X, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Mic Geronimo, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Michel'le, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - Milk, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 47)
      - Meek Mills, 2012-2013 (Box 24, Folder 48)
      - Jae Millz, No Date (Box 24, Folder 49)
      - Mims, 2007-2009 (Box 24, Folder 50)
      - Nikki Minaj, 2010-2013 (Box 24, Folder 51)
      - Mister Cee, 2008-2013 (Box 24, Folder 52)
      - Mix Master Mike, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 53)
      - Mobb Deep
        - Mobb Deep '93-'11, 1993-2006 (Box 24, Folder 54)
        - Mobb Deep photos, 1993-2000 (Box 24, Folder 55)
        - Mobb Deep '04, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 56)
      - Modern music man/ AJ Woodson, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 57)
      - M.O.P., 1993-2002 (Box 24, Folder 58)
      - Joan Morgan, No Date (Box 24, Folder 59)
      - Marcyliena Morgan, 2003-2013 (Box 24, Folder 60)
      - Mos Def, 1999-2012 (Box 24, Folder 61)
      - Minister Conrad Muhammad, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 62)
      - muMs a/k/a muMs da Schemer, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 63)
      - Murder Dog (magazine), 1995 (Box 24, Folder 64)
      - Murder Inc., 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 65)
      - "Murder was the Case" (soundtrack), 1994 (Box 24, Folder 66)
      - Keith Murray, 1995-2010 (Box 24, Folder 67)
      - Murs, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 68)
      - Russell Myrie, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 69)
      - Mystikal
        - Mystikal '95-'04, 1995-2004 (Box 24, Folder 70)
        - Mystikal '95-'13, 1999-2013 (Box 24, Folder 71)
      - Nappy Roots, 2002-2011 (Box 24, Folder 72)
      - Nas
        - Nas '90s, 1994-1999 (Box 24, Folder 73)
        - Nas '00-'10, 2000-2010 (Box 24, Folder 74)
        - Nas '11-'13, 2011-2013 (Box 24, Folder 75)
      - Nate Dogg, 1998, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Naughty by Nature, 1991-2002, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Necro, 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Nefertiti, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Nelly, 2000-2010 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Neptunes, N.E.R.D., and Pharrell Williams, 2000-2013 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - "New Jack City" (movie), 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - "New Jersey Drive" (movie), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - New Kingdom, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Ne-Yo, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Nice and Smooth, 1990-1994, 2001-2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Pete Nice and Daddy Rich, 1992-1993, 2010-2011 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Nikki D, 1990-1993, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Nikki D photo by Tim Carter, No Date; CD-2145 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - 95 South, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - No Face, 1991-1994 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - No I.D., 2005 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Nonchalant, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Non-Phixion, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Noreaga a/k/a N.O.R.E., 1998-2013 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - O.C., 1994 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Odd Future, including Tyler the Creator, Frank Ocean, Earl Sweatshirt, 2010-2013 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Old Dirty Bastard a/k/a ODB
        - Old Dirty Bastard, 1992-2012 (Box 25, Folder 23)
        - Old Dirty Bastard copies of press clippings, 1998-2008 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Shaquille O'Neal, 1992-2002 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - The Onion (newspaper), 2001 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Onyx
        - Onyx Photos, 1992-1993undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
        - Onyx lyrics, 1995, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
        - Onyx press '92-'93, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 29)
        - Onyx- inter-office memos, 1991-1995 (Box 25, Folder 30)
        - Onyx press '95, 1995 (2001) (Box 25, Folder 31)
        - Onyx press materials '95, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 32)
        - Onyx tour '95, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 33)
        - Onyx '96-'06, 1996-2006 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Organized Konfusion, 1991-1997 (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - Original Flavor, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - Originoo Gunn Clappaz, No Date (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Outkast
        - Outkast II Aquemini, 1994, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 38)
        - Outkast, 1994-2012 (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - Outlaw Posse, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Outlawz, 2001-2007 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Petey Pablo, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 42)
      - Paperboy, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - Pastor Troy, 2001-2007 (Box 25, Folder 44)
      - Patra, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - Sean Paul, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 46)
      - Peanut Butter Wolf, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 47)
      - Pen and Pixel (album cover design), 1996-2000 (Box 25, Folder 48)
      - Paula Perry, No Date (Box 25, Folder 49)
      - The Pharcyde, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 50)
      - Philly's Most Wanted, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 51)
      - Pitbull, 2003-2012 (Box 25, Folder 52)
      - Lesley Pitts, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      - The Players Club, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 54)
      - Plies, 2008-2010 (Box 25, Folder 55)
      - PMD, 1994-2003 (Box 25, Folder 56)
      - Poison Clan, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 57)
      - Pooh-Man, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 58)
      - Positive K, 1992-1993, 2008-2010 (Box 25, Folder 59)
      - Kevin Powell, 1995-2006 (Box 25, Folder 60)
      - Pretty Tone Capone, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 61)
      - Sean Price, 2006-2010 (Box 25, Folder 62)
      - Prince Paul
        - Prince Paul "Among Thieves" (film), 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 63)
        - Prince Paul '87-'11, 1987-2011 (Box 25, Folder 64)
        - Prince Paul, No Date; CD-2146 (Box 25, Folder 64)
        - "The Diary of Prince Paul" (documentary film), 2003; DVD-1078 (Box 25, Folder 64)
        - Prince Paul's "Handsome Boy Modeling School", 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 67)
      - Princess Superstar, No Date (Box 25, Folder 68)
      - Prince Rahiem, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 69)
      - Prodigy, 2000-2013 (Box 25, Folder 70)
      - Professor X, 1993, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 71)
      - Project Pat, 1999-2007 (Box 25, Folder 72)
      - Pusha T, 2011-2013 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - Performer Names Q-Z
      - Q-Tip, 1998-2003 (Box 25, Folder 74)
      - Quad City DJs, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 75)
      - Queen Mother Rage, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 76)
      - Queen Pen, 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 77)
      - Raekwon, 1995-2012 (Box 25, Folder 78)
      - R.A. the Rugged Man, No Date (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Rah Digga, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Rahzel, 1999-2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Rakim (Solo), 1991-2012 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Rap Archives, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Rap-A-Lot (record label), 1993, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Rap and Fashion, 1982-2012 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Rap and Guns (and violence), 1988-2002 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Rap and Homophobia, 1993-2003, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Rap and Movies, 1991-2000 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Rap and Radio, 1990-1993 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Rap and Women, 1990-2004 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Rap Genius, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Rap Glossaries, 1984-1990, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Rap Miscellaneous, 1990-1999 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Rappin' 4-Tay, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Rap Videos for VH1, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Ras Kass, 1995-2001 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Brett Ratner, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Raw Breed, c. 1997 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Raw Fusiion, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Rawkus (record label), 2004 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - "Red Hot & Rap" (album and TV special), 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 23)
        AIDS prevention project
      - Red Hot Lover Tone, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Redman
        - Redman photos, c. 1994-2004 (Box 26, Folder 25)
        - Redman '90s, 1993-1999 (2008) (Box 26, Folder 26)
        - Redman '00-'11, 2001-2011 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Remedy, No Date (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - Remy Ma, 2005-2010 (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - Resident Alien, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - "Rhyme and Reason" (documentary film), 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Richie Rich, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 32)
      - Rihanna, 2005-2013 (Box 26, Folder 33)
      - Ronin Ro, 1996-2008 (Box 26, Folder 34)
      - Pete Rock and C.L. Smooth, 1989-2006 (Box 26, Folder 35)
      - Rockwilder, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 36)
      - Rodney O and Joe Cooley, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 37)
      - The Roots, 1994-2013 (Box 26, Folder 38)
      - Tricia Rose, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 39)
      - Rick Ross, 2006-2013 (Box 26, Folder 40)
      - Royce da 5'9", 1999-2004,2012 (Box 26, Folder 41)
      - Ruffhouse (record label), 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 42)
      - Ruff Ryders, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 43)
      - Rumpletilskinz, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 44)
      - RZA a/k/a The RZA, 1998-2013 (Box 26, Folder 45)
      - Sadat X, 1996, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 46)
      - Theda Sandiford, c. 1999-2004 (Box 26, Folder 47)
      - Kelefa Sanneh a/k/a K. Sanneh, 1999-2012 (Box 26, Folder 48)
      - Juelz Santana, 2004-2013 (Box 26, Folder 49)
      - Sauce Money, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 50)
      - "Scarface" (movie), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 51)
      - Scarface (rapper), 1993-2008 (Box 26, Folder 52)
      - Scarface (record label), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 53)
      - Scoob and Scrap Lover, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 54)
      - Screwball, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 55)
      - 2nd II None, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 56)
      - MC Serch, 1992-2011 (Box 26, Folder 57)
      - Erick Sermon, 1988-2011 (Box 26, Folder 58)
      - Shaggy, 1995-2007 (Box 26, Folder 59)
      - Sha-Key, No Date (Box 26, Folder 60)
      - Sham and the Professor, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 61)
      - Shawnna, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 62)
      - Shawty Lo, 2013 (Box 26, Folder 63)
      - Sheek Louch, 2007-2010 (Box 26, Folder 64)
      - "The Show" (documentary film), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 65)
      - Showbiz and A.G., 1995-2005 (Box 26, Folder 66)
      - Shyne, 2000-2011 (Box 26, Folder 67)
      - Beanie Sigel, 2000-2007 (Box 26, Folder 68)
      - Silkk the Shocker, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 69)
      - Kimora Lee Simmons
        - Kimora ads, 1997-2008 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Kimora Lee Simmons '00-'10, 2000-2013 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Skee-lo, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Slim Thug and Boss Hogg, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Slum Village, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Smif-n-Wessun, 1994-1995, 2005, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Danyel Smith, 1993-2009 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Will Smith
        - Will Smith '90-'04, 1990-2004 (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - Will Smith '04, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - Will Smith '05-'06, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 10)
        - Will Smith '07-'13, 2007-2013 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Smithsonian Institution (National Museum of American History acquires hip-hop collection.)
        - Smithsonian '06, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - Smithsonian '06, 2006, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - Smithsonian '13, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Smoothe Da Hustler, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - "Snaps" (book), 2001 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Snoop Dogg a/k/a Snoop Doggy Dogg
        - Snoop Doggy Dogg, 1993-2003 (Box 27, Folder 17)
        - Snoop '03, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 18)
        - Snoop '04, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 19)
        - Snoop '05, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 20)
        - Ads featuring Snoop '93-'04, 1993-2004 (Box 27, Folder 21)
        - Snoop '06-'13, 2006-2013 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Snow, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Son of Bazerk, 1990-1991, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Sista Souljah, 1990-2013 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Soulja Boy, 2007-2011 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Soulja Slim, No Date (Box 27, Folder 27)
      - Souls of Mischief, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      - South Africa, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      - South Central Cartel, 1993-1995, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - Bubba Sparxx, 2002-2006 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      - Spearhead
        - Spearhead photos, 1992-1996 (Box 27, Folder 32)
        - Spearhead publicity shots, c. 1994 (Box 27, Folder 33)
        - Spearhead '94, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 34)